Guide to the International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 66 Records WAG.010
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series IV: Shop Files, 1937-1979, 4
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions. Promulgated by the PA in 1970, the LRI provided for an unilateral panel to hear labor disputes. Internal hearings held by the PA Commission heard the objections of the several PA unions. Further objections were taken to the state level (including the Public Employment Relations Board; State senate bills 8810 and 8973 in 1972). In 1976, an "independent" panel (the PA Employment Relations Board) was established by law to replace the LRI panel. Records include documents of the internal and state hearings, bills, correspondence from the unions, drafts of the proposed labor instructions, procedures for representation, precedents, testimonies by Local 66, AFL-CIO legislative pamphlets, Joint Gubernatorial Committee reports, resumes for selection of panelists for the new PA Employment Relations Board., 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Port Authority: Labor Relations Instructions [see 26/27], 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Port Authority: Organizing - includes surveys on work attitudes, member's essay on working conditions, PA "career plan", recruitment lists, examples of unfair labor practices, 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Port Authority: Organizing [see 27/1], 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Port Authority: Organizing [see 27/1], 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Port Authority: Organizing [see 27/1], 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Port Authority: Organizing [see 27/1], 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Port Authority: Organizing [see 27/1], 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Port Authority: Organizing [see 27/1], 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Port Authority: Organizing [see 27/1], 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Port Authority: Representation election: petitions, 1978? (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Port Authority: Representation election: petitions, 1978? (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Port Authority: Tenure withdrawal - union appeal against new PA policy to remove job security provisions for professionals. Includes earlier PA policy documents (beginning 1941) and PA statement on history of autonomy, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Port Authority: Tenure withdrawal [see 27/11], 1969 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Port Authority: Tenure withdrawal [see 27/11], 1969 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Port Authority: Tenure withdrawal [see 27/11], 1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Port Authority: Tenure withdrawal [see 27/11], 1969 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Port Authority: Tenure withdrawal [see 27/11], 1969 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Port Authority: Tenure withdrawal [see 27/11], 1969 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Port Authority: Tenure withdrawal [see 27/11], 1969 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion - salary increases, reduction in force (RIF), promotion plans, overtime pay. Campaigns, petitions, company plans, labor-management notes., 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Port Authority: Pay and promotion [see 27/19], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Port Authority: Grievances, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Port Authority: Benefits: health and retirement. Debate on insufficient coverage and lack of benefits for "annual" workers., 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Port Authority: Benefits [see 27/44], 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Port Authority: Benefits [see 27/44], 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Port Authority: Press clippings about PA and union issues (includes analysis of big banking interests in PA), 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Port Authority: Press clippings about PA and union issues (includes analysis of big banking interests in PA), 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Port Authority: Press clippings about PA and union issues (includes analysis of big banking interests in PA), 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Port Authority: Press clippings about PA and union issues (includes analysis of big banking interests in PA), 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Port Authority: Press clippings about PA and union issues (includes analysis of big banking interests in PA), 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Port Authority: Press clippings about PA and union issues (includes analysis of big banking interests in PA), 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Port Authority: Company documents: minutes, memos, management bulletins, circulars to employees (sampled), 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Port Authority: Company documents [see 27/53], 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Port Authority: Documents and correspondence from other unions, US Dept of Labor, White Collar Report, 1967-1978 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Port Authority: Documents and correspondence from other unions, US Dept of Labor, White Collar Report, 1967-1978 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Port Authority: Documents and correspondence from other unions, US Dept of Labor, White Collar Report, 1967-1978 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Port Authority: Documents and correspondence from other unions, US Dept of Labor, White Collar Report, 1967-1978 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Pension issue - unions, companies and press debate the (1973) state plan to reduce public employee pension benefits., 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Pension issue [see 28/1], 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Pension issue [see 28/1], 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Pension issue [see 28/1], 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Pension issue [see 28/1], 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Pension issue [see 28/1], 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Pension issue [see 28/1], 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Pension issue [see 28/1], 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Lists - employees, job specifications, salaries, guild membership, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Lists [see 28/9], 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Lists [see 28/9], 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Lists [see 28/9], 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Lists [see 28/9], 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Lists [see 28/9], 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Lists [see 28/9], 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: Union newsletters and circulars: Guild Newsletter and Project, draft materials and notes., 1969-1979 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: [See 28/17], 1969-1979 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: [See 28/17], 1969-1979 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: [See 28/17], 1969-1979 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: [See 28/17], 1969-1979 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Oversize: Port Authority: [See 28/17], 1969-1979 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Oversize: Collective bargaining: Models and Research notes., 1950-1966 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Oversize: Collective bargaining: Models and Research notes., 1950-1966 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Oversize: Collective bargaining: Models and Research notes., 1950-1966 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Oversize: AFTE conventions: Resolutions and amendments, 1976, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Oversize: AFTE conventions: Resolutions and amendments, 1976, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Oversize: Dues receipt book; begins with charter affiliation members, 1937 (Box 28)
  - Oversize: Daily receipts and expenditures ledger., 1939-1941 (Box 28)
  - Oversize: Photographs (see also Souvenir Publications for photos), Undated (Box 28)
  - Oversize: Foster-Wheeler Corporation: circulars to employees, 1945-1948 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Oversize: R. Hoe: Employee surveys by union, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Oversize: Horn Construction: labor/management disputes includes copy of company's minutes (Field Engineers Strike), 1950-1952 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Oversize: John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation documents, 1950-1956 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Oversize: John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation documents, 1950-1956 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Oversize: John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation documents, 1950-1956 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Oversize: John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation documents, 1950-1956 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Oversize: John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation documents, 1950-1956 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Oversize: John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation documents, 1950-1956 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Oversize: John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation documents, 1950-1956 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Oversize: John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation documents, 1950-1956 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Oversize: Lederle Laboratory: Employee surveys by union, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Oversize: Lummus Co.: representation (NLRB runoff with FAECT-CIO rival union), 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Oversize: Marble Industry: Representation (SLRB affidavits...), 1941 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Oversize: Mergenthaler Linotype: employee surveys, representation (Local 66 and rival Local 18), press clippings, contracts, 1951-1968 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Oversize: Mergenthaler Linotype: [See 29/15], 1951-1968 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Oversize: Mergenthaler Linotype: [See 29/15], 1951-1968 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Oversize: Mergenthaler Linotype: [See 29/15], 1951-1968 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Oversize: Mergenthaler Linotype: [See 29/15], 1951-1968 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Oversize: Mergenthaler Linotype: [See 29/15], 1951-1968 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Oversize: Otis Elevator Co. Organizing (election won by FAECT-CIO), office workers on strike (UAW-UOPWA), flyers, 1943-1950 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Oversize: Prodex: contracts, 1966-1972 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Oversize: Reeves Instrument Co.: certification (NLRB), briefs, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Oversize: Royal Switchboard Co.: negotiations notes, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Oversize: Sperry: bulletins of Sperry Engineers Association, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Oversize: Superior Fireproof Door and Sash Co.: Events leading to unfair labor charge; workplace procedures with diagrams., 1957-1961 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Oversize: Superior Fireproof Door and Sash Co.: Events leading to unfair labor charge; workplace procedures with diagrams., 1957-1961 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Oversize: Superior Fireproof Door and Sash Co.: Events leading to unfair labor charge; workplace procedures with diagrams., 1957-1961 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Oversize: Superior Fireproof Door and Sash Co.: Events leading to unfair labor charge; workplace procedures with diagrams., 1957-1961 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Oversize: Western Electric - Kearny Works: organizing leaflets, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Oversize: S.S. White and Pennwalt Co. (merger): Industrial Union. Dept negotiations, national conference, company reports and press, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Series V: Finances, Membership Records, and General Files (Unprocessed), circa 1935-1984, 5
  - Local financial audit reports (in cardstock binders), 1942-1959 (Box 30)
  - Per Capita Tax reports to international (gives size of membership each year or month), 1937-1947, 1956-1961 (Box 30)
  - AFTE Financial reports (see also Minutes of Exec. Board), 1955-1960 (Box 30)
  - Financial reports of the local, CIB, and others, 1948-1962 (Box 30)
  - Trust Fund resolutions and correspondence (strike fund), 1949-1973 (Box 30)
  - Retirement plan for fulltime office employees of Local 66, 1960-1965 (Box 30)
  - Financial correspondence and bills (sampled): Strike contributions, dinners, Department of Labor Reports, taxes, special accounts, new members lists, 1950s-1960s (Box 30)
  - Check-off lists (samples give members per shop), 1960s (Box 30)
  - Expenses accounts (sampled), 1960s (Box 30)
  - Affiliations (per capita taxes), 1960 (Box 30)
  - Bulletins of Local 66, (incomplete series for 1934, 1965, 1977-1979) (chronological folders), 1935-1979, 1934, 1965, 1977-1979 (Box 31)
  - Membership dues book with alphabetic index of charter members, 1937-ca. 1944 (Box 32)
  - Monthly balances of the Division accounts, by division, 1941-1948 (Box 32)
  - Cash disbursements journal (daily check entries), 1948-1959 (Box 33)
  - Shop files: Employee rate changes, terminations, new hires for Lummus, Lederle Lab, Mergenthaler, General Bronze, S.S. White, R. Hoe (Box 34)
  - Welfare and retirement funds: OIB Retirement and Welfare Fund minutes, 1951-1976 (Box 35)
  - Welfare and retirement funds: OIB Fund changes and handbooks, 1958-1975 (Box 35)
  - Welfare and retirement funds: OIB Participants Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 35)
  - Welfare and retirement funds: OIB Welfare Fund agreement, 1950-1952 (Box 35)
  - Welfare and retirement funds: OIB Fund annual and financial reports, correspondence, "documents", employer contributions, pension rejections, pension receipts per employee, 1950s-1960s (Box 35)
  - Welfare and retirement funds: Technical Employees Benefits Trust (TEBT: R. Hoe Co. and Local 66 joint trust): contracts, audits, correspondence, 1957-1966 (Box 35)
  - Welfare and retirement funds: Additional Benefit funds records (OIB, TEBT). (Box 36)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1960-1980 (Box 37)
  - Weekly Reports, 1940-1960 (Box 38)
  - Membership files (Box 39)
  - Membership files (Box 40)
  - Membership files (Box 41)
  - Membership files (Box 42)
  - Membership files (Box 43)
  - Membership files (Box 44)
  - Membership files (Box 45)
  - Membership files (Box 46)
  - Membership files (Box 47)
  - Membership files (Box 48)
  - Membership files (Box 49)
  - Membership files (Box 50)
  - Membership files (Box 51)
  - Membership files (Box 52)
  - Membership files (Box 53)
  - Membership files (Box 54)
  - Membership files (Box 55)
  - Membership files (Box 56)
  - Membership files (Box 57)
  - Membership files (Box 58)
  - Membership files (Box 59)
  - Membership files (Box 60)
  - Membership files (Box 61)
  - Membership files (Box 62)
  - Membership files (Box 63)
  - Membership files (Box 64)
  - Membership files (Box 65)
  - Membership files (Box 66)
  - Membership files (Box 67)
  - Membership files (Box 68)
  - Membership files (Box 69)
  - Shop files: Foster-Wheeler, 1948-1962 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: General Bronze, 1937-1944 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: Laboratory Furniture, 1959 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: Lummus, 1952-1956 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: Ment Brothers, 1942-1949 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: R. Hoe (Box 70)
  - Shop files: Pomeroy, 1959 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: Ferdinand Muller, 1939-1949 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: Standard Switchboard, 1942-1949 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: SS White, 1960 (Box 70)
  - Shop files: AP Wins Iron and Bronze (Box 70)
  - New York Federation of Labor, 1955 (Box 70)
  - IUD, 1960 (Box 70)
  - National Council of Marine Draftsmen, 1938-1940 (Box 70)
  - Association of Engineers, 1943 (Box 70)
  - Business manager files, 1957-1962 (Box 70)
  - Executive Board, 1955-1959 (Box 70)
  - IFEADU Executive Board, 1942-1943 (Box 70)
  - AFTE files, 1954-1960 (Box 70)
  - Field Engineers and Surveyors Strike, 1950-1954 (Box 70)
  - Organizing files, 1964-1965 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, Local 371, 1956-1957 (Box 70)
  - Correspondence with Lummus Company, 1960-1982 (Box 71)
  - Lummus Company grievance file, 1960s-1980s (Box 71)
  - Bargaining unit activity records, 1980-1984 (Box 71)
  - Engineering and Professional Guild Seniority List, 1984 (Box 71)
  - Technical Committee minutes, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Notes on a meeting with management and others, 1985 (Box 71)
  - List of recalls, 1984 (Box 71)
  - Various agreements, 1980s (Box 71)
  - Adjusted hire dates at Combustion Engineering, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Rates of members list, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Lummus contract summary, 1981 (Box 71)
  - List of nominees for stewardship, 1984 (Box 71)
  - Unidentified notebooks (Box 71)
  - Electrical Division, 1940-1950 (Box 72)
  - Hollow Metal Division files, 1948-1967 (Box 72)
  - Machinery Division, 1951-1957 (Box 72)
  - Oil Refinery and Chemical Plant Division, 1962-1964 (Box 72)
  - Ornamental Iron and Bronze Division, 1944-1971 (Box 72)
  - Pearl River Division, 1950-1967 (Box 72)
  - Richman Division, 1962-1965 (Box 72)
  - Telephone call logbooks, 1957-1959 (Box 73)
  - Port Authority Personnel Department newsletter, 1974-1978 (Box 73)
  - Contract negotiations (Box 73)
  - Marble Division, 1955-1961 (Box 73)
  - Honesdale Division, 1955-1961 (Box 73)
  - Unfiled documents (Box 73)
  - Telephone call logbooks, 1951-1961 (Box 74)
  - Shop files and division files, 1940s-1950s (Box 74)
  - Binder of shop documents from Pennwalt Corporation, 1976-1983 (Box 75)
  - Binder of shop documents from Pennwalt Corporation, 1938-1978 (Box 75)
  - Constitution and By-laws booklets, 1957, 1965, 1968, 1981 (Box 75)
  - Pennwalt/SS White General Rules and Information booklet (Box 75)
  - Layoff list, Engineering Guild, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Grievance review meeting, Aug 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Job Code #410: Parts list compiler (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Union: George Schron (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Seniority lists (samples: 1965 and 1982) (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Otto Kettling (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - John M. Hayden (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Grievance Notes and Related Data (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Grievances (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Grievance Notes (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Negotiations (schedules), 1964 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Negotiations, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Contract Negotiations (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Family Dental Center (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Request for leave of absence under Article 16.1 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Grievance: Guild v. Pennwalt SS White re: Violation, article 14, seniority H. Hock (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Guild v. SS White, re: Violation of Article 23, Funeral leave (payment for time lost). Grievance filed by Debra Phibbs, October 29, 1982, Oct 1982 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Contract, Technical personnel (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Guild job postings (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Forms: Job award request (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Occupational safety and health standards / OSHA (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Seminars: Human Resources Development and Negotiations (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Grievance on behalf of John Hayden: Personal time test case (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Grievance: Local 66 v. SS White re: Violation of (Local 66) Guilds Sectional Seniority (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Grievance: Guild v. SS White Engineering Management. Violation of Addendum A, Job Function (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Grievance: Guild v. SS White Engineering Management. Violation of Addendum A, Job Function (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Grievance: Disrespect shown a Guild member by a member of Management (Re: Memo written by J. Helmer in reference to P. Cammarano) (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Grievance: Honor Roll for Owen Sleight (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Grievance: Guild v. SS White. Violation of Past Practice: Payment for lost time (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Grievance: Guild v. SS White, re: Disproportionate overtime allocation (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Grievance: Article V. of the Contract Guild v SS White. Re: M. Moroz (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Grievance: Local 66 / Holmdel Chapter v. Pennwalt/SS White, re: Union Security / Article XXIII (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Bill Evans 1966 status report upon resignation (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Previous chairman notes and data; H. Splund and V. Ripary [spelling?] (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Lummus Company correspondence and other documents, including pension plan and contract negotiations notes, 1980-1983 (Box 76)
  - Jessor shop files; Membership list; Misc. documents (Box 77)
  - Lummus Company agreements, correspondence, seniority lists; Constitution and Bylaws, Local 66 (Box 78)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Contract negotiations, 1976-1978 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Contract negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Info. Re: Retro Pay Dir Contract (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Job descriptions (Box 78, Folder 4)